Guide to the Walter Freeman, Class of 1916, Yale College, Photograph Albums Documenting Life at Yale
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Volume V (?)
  - Page 75
    - 2118. After the game (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2119. PBK--faculty, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2120-24. [Baseball] (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Page 76
    - 2125. Dutch Carter, Quinky (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2126-27. Baseball (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2128. Handy (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2129. Yale Baseball team (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - 2130. [Baseball] (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Page 77
    - 2131. Izzy Winters (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2132. New rink (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2133. Gun Club house burns (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2134. Mack, Queal (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2135. Stick work at the new rink (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2136. Lake Whitney (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2137. [Track] (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2138. Lake Whitney--ice hockey (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2139. Lake Whitney (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Page 78
    - 2140. Ran McDonald, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2141. Labowitz (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2142. Maxim (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2143. [Hockey] (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2144-45. [Gymnastics] (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - 2146. Schiller (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Page 79
    - 2147. Phelps (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2148. Byers (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2149. Slides on ice (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2150. Princeton eating club (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Page 80
    - 2151. Byers Hall, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2152. Down Library Street (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2153. Commons (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2154. Hillhouse property during 1913-14 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2155. The early stages of the Bowl (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2156. Jim Donnelly (died 1914 Nov) (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - 2157. Campus during snowstorm (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Page 81
    - 2158. Crew (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2159. Spring regatta, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2160. Ferry, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2161. Fall regatta, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2162. New London, 1st Freshman, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2163. Tener, Snowden (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2164. Building new stadium, 1913 Feb (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2165. Sprints 1914--Gaillard wins single sculls (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2166. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Page 82
    - 2167. Fall regatta (1st Sheff vs. 1st AC Sheff), 1912 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2168-69. Crew (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2170. Cox: Barnum; 8: Lippincott; 4: Philbin; 2: Bryer (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2171. Harvard (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2172. Rogers, Denman, Romeyn (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2173. Gilfillan (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - 2174. Crew (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Page 83
    - 2175. Judge's Cave (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2176. Battell (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2177. CCNY (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2178. Leland Stanford (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2179. Observatory (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2180. Gales Ferry, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2181. Calcium light night from Conn., 1912 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2182. Osborn Labs (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Page 84
    - 2183. From the Taft, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2184. Art School (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2185. After Sunday chapel (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - 2186. Old Campus by night (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Page 85
    - 2187. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2188. Percy Wendell (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2189. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2190. [Soccer] (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2191-93. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2194. McDevitt (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2195. Vaughn (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2196. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Page 86
    - 2197. Wilson, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2198-2201. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2202. Hunter (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - 2203-05. [Football] (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Page 87
    - 2206. Fall 1914--1st Denham varsity (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2207. A.M. Munson, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2208. Baseball picnic to Madison, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2209. 1st University crew (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2210. Swinert (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2211. Fall regatta--1st AC Freshmen, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2212-2214. Regatta (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Page 88
    - 2215. Waiting (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2216. Breaking the ice (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2217. Freshmen (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2218. 1st AC varsity, fall, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2219. Regatta (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2220. BB picnic (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2221. McHenry (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - 2222. Yale crew (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Page 89
    - 2223. Bones (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2224. Memorial Hall (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2225. Byers (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2226. Quadrangle, Penn (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2227. Gould Hall, award (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2228. Sophomore baseball (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2229. Phelps (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Page 90
    - 2230. CT Hall, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2231. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2232. Morris Cove (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2233. Near Wright Gate (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2234. Phelps Gate (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - 2235. Wright Hall (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Page 91
    - 2236. Memorial Day (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2237. [1916], 1912 September 26 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2238. German band, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2239-2240. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2241. H.R. Hawley, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Page 92
    - 2242. Brown game parade (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2243. Penn freshman rush, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2244-2246. [Fraternity], 1913 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2247. Princeton hazing (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2248. Parade (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - 2249. 1913 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Page 93
    - 2250. Fresh (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2251. Yale vs. Princeton baseball, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2252. [Baseball] (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2253. Princeton baseball, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2254. Cormish, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2255-57. Baseball (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Page 94
    - 2258. Quniby, Blossom (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2259. Note the ball (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2260. Brown baseball, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2261. Pumpelly, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2262. Baseball squad taking the car to the field (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2263. Bench, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2264. Tufts baseball, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - 2265-66. Baseball (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Page 95
    - 2267. Spaulding, Ketchum, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - 2268. Brown, football, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - 2269. Football (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Page 96
    - 2270. Football, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - 2271. Spaulding makes a touchdown, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - 2272. RTP Stover H., Y 1914 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - 2273-74. Football (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Page 97
    - 2275. Unidentified room (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2276. Lit board, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2277. Dwight Grill (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2278. Woodfire talk at Byers (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2279. Library shelves (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2280. Abolishing the Feb 22 rush, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2281. Unidentified group of students (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Page 98
    - 2282. From Phelps (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2283. What chance has a pedestrian (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2284. City express men (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - 2285. 8:20 AM (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Page 99
    - 2286. Fencing (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2287. Everard (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2288. Dartmouth Winter Carnival (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2289. Lake Whitney (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2290. G.E. Brown, 1914S (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2291. Hockey player (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2292. Lake Whitney (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2293. Everard (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2294. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - Page 100
    - 2295. Smith (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2296. Herman, Stackpole (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2297. Swihart, Dunn (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2298. Arnold (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2299. Sweney (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2300. Heron (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2301. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2302. Harper (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2303. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2304. Armory rifle range (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2305-2307. Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - 2308. Quentin Durward rehearsal, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 177)
- Photocopies and caption list (Box 6, Folder 1)